[{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980267429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":36915,"timeElapsed":111939},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980283477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":16046,"timeElapsed":127986},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980302468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":18991,"timeElapsed":146978},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980313861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":11392,"timeElapsed":158371},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980325517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":11655,"timeElapsed":170027},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980332149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":6631,"timeElapsed":176659},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980336524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4375,"timeElapsed":181034},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980353893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":17368,"timeElapsed":198403},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980363621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":9727,"timeElapsed":208131},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":20975,"timeElapsed":230827},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980391788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5470,"timeElapsed":236298},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980399804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":8015,"timeElapsed":244314},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980404085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4279,"timeElapsed":248595},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4511,"timeElapsed":253107},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980412269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3671,"timeElapsed":256779},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980416117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3847,"timeElapsed":260627},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980422269,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6151,"timeElapsed":266779},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433525,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":11255,"timeElapsed":278035},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980438781,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5255,"timeElapsed":283291},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":20871,"timeElapsed":305539},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980466348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":5319,"timeElapsed":310858},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980472101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":5752,"timeElapsed":316611},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980476285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4183,"timeElapsed":320795},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980480197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3912,"timeElapsed":324707},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980483189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2991,"timeElapsed":327699},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980486932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3743,"timeElapsed":331442},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980494436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":7503,"timeElapsed":338946},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980497814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3377,"timeElapsed":342324},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980509245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":10167,"timeElapsed":353755},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980512789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3543,"timeElapsed":357299},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5463,"timeElapsed":362762},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3848,"timeElapsed":366611},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980526501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4399,"timeElapsed":371011},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980531909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":5407,"timeElapsed":376418},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980534997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3087,"timeElapsed":379507},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980544197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":9199,"timeElapsed":388707},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980547893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3695,"timeElapsed":392403},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980558085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":8815,"timeElapsed":402595},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3943,"timeElapsed":406539},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3799,"timeElapsed":410338},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2552,"timeElapsed":412891},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980571804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3423,"timeElapsed":416314},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2304,"timeElapsed":418619},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980576845,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2736,"timeElapsed":421355},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980580597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3751,"timeElapsed":425107},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980583725,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3127,"timeElapsed":428235},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980593158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8177,"timeElapsed":437668},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980595757,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2598,"timeElapsed":440267},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7551,"timeElapsed":447819},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980606053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2743,"timeElapsed":450562},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980609165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3112,"timeElapsed":453675},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980611613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2448,"timeElapsed":456123},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980614804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3191,"timeElapsed":459314},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980619037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4232,"timeElapsed":463547},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980621597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2559,"timeElapsed":466107},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":8624,"timeElapsed":475979},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980633637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2167,"timeElapsed":478147},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980638901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5263,"timeElapsed":483411},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980640909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2007,"timeElapsed":485419},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980644196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3287,"timeElapsed":488706},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655861,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11664,"timeElapsed":500371},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980659213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3351,"timeElapsed":503723},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980662973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3759,"timeElapsed":507483},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":8055,"timeElapsed":515539},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980673236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"44","question":"Do you think of yourself as creative? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2207,"timeElapsed":517746},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980683469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":9104,"timeElapsed":527979},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980686093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2624,"timeElapsed":530603},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980690021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3927,"timeElapsed":534531},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2080,"timeElapsed":536611},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980694525,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2423,"timeElapsed":539035},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980697117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2591,"timeElapsed":541627},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980699357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2239,"timeElapsed":543867},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980703389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4031,"timeElapsed":547899},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980705485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2096,"timeElapsed":549995},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980720900,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":14200,"timeElapsed":565410},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980723661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2760,"timeElapsed":568171},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980730198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":6537,"timeElapsed":574708},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980733125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2926,"timeElapsed":577635},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980736637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3511,"timeElapsed":581147},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980739548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2910,"timeElapsed":584058},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980742158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2609,"timeElapsed":586668},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980746557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4398,"timeElapsed":591066},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980749484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2927,"timeElapsed":593994},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980757453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":6855,"timeElapsed":601963},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980760309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2855,"timeElapsed":604819},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980763397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3087,"timeElapsed":607907},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980765781,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2383,"timeElapsed":610291},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980768980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3199,"timeElapsed":613490},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980772181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":3200,"timeElapsed":616691},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774948,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2766,"timeElapsed":619458},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980779646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4697,"timeElapsed":624156},{"subjectID":"vzqgpcbbhp","prolificID":"665a1158d75699007466a154","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224b2fa8bee082b6f96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980781957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2310,"timeElapsed":626467}]